wealthresult.com 2017-05-27

# Privacy Policy | WealthResult.com

We do not share personal information with third-parties nor do we store information we collect about your visit to this blog for use other than to analyze content performance through the use of cookies, which you can turn off at anytime by modifying your Internet browser’s settings. This privacy policy is subject to change without notice.

**Privacy Regarding Tracking by Third-Parties**

WealthResult.com uses DoubleClick, Google, and other third-party Ad Servers to serve and display Advertisements on this site. WealthResult.com does not provide personally identifiable information to Ad Servers. These Ad Servers and Advertisers may use cookies, pixel trackers, or other internet technology to improve the effectiveness and targeting of Advertisements to you within this site and any other place where that third-party is serving Advertisements.

WealthResult.com does not have access to, nor control over, advertisers’ or ad service providers’ cookies or how they may be used or how they were collected. In many cases, this information could be used to show you ads based on your interests on other Web sites.

You have options and choices about the collection and use of information by third-parties on WealthResult.com:

If you wish to opt out of Advertising companies tracking and tailoring advertisements to your surfing patterns you may do so within the Network Advertising Initiative

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to WealthResult.com or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page.

If a user wish to subscribe to our email updates (provided through Mailchimp and Feedburner), we ask for only email address and names. This subscriptions provide easy tools for users of The Said Service to opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party. We hate Spam as much as you do.

This privacy policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You may wish to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site and/or your registration for any of our products or services constitutes an acceptance of this privacy policy.

**Comment Policy**

Comments are welcomed and encouraged on this site, but there are some instances where comments will be edited or deleted as follows:

  *     Comments deemed to be spam or questionable will be deleted. Including a link to relevant content is permitted, but comments should be relevant to the post topic.
  *     Comments including profanity will be deleted.
  *     Comments containing language or concepts that could be deemed offensive will be deleted.
  *     Comments that attack a person individually will be deleted.

We The Owners of WealthResult.com reserves the right to edit or delete any comments submitted to this blog without notice. This comment policy is subject to change at anytime.

**HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS USED**

The use of your information depends on your consent. By visiting WealthResult.com, you agree to have  “cookies”, log files and/or “clear GIFs” stored onto your computer/web browser, which will not be shared with other companies.

**Personal Information:** We do not share, sell, or buy personal information. We may share the Personal Information we collect from you only with your consent. The information you submit is used only for internal purposes and to provide quality customer service to you as well as to send you our latest updates.

**Protection of rights:** We may release Personal Information or other information we collect from you if we believe that such action is appropriate to: (I) comply with legal requests and processes; (II) identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who are or we believe have caused or might cause injury to us or a third party; (III) defend or respond to claims brought or threatened against PALNESS MEDIA, its employees, direct sellers, suppliers, service providers, installers, users of our Services or others; or (IV) otherwise protect or assert the rights, property, interests or personal safety of PALNESS MEDIA, its employees, direct sellers, suppliers, service providers, installers, users of the Services or others. Any such release decisions may be made by us in our sole discretion.

**Record Keeping:** It may be necessary for PALNESS MEDIA to keep records of certain Personal Information you have provided to us or which we have obtained from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy for business purposes.

**Non-personal Information:** Information that is automatically gathered, including through the use of cookies (as defined above), may be shared among our Websites, if applicable.

Notifications of claimed infringement should be forwarded to: admin@palness.com
